Can i help you?
需要帮忙吗？
Yes, I've just moved to this area with my wife and children and I'd like to know where we can all register with a doctor at a Health Centre.
是的，我刚和我的妻子、孩子搬到这里，我想知道我们在哪里可以与健康中心的医生登记。
Okay. Well, there's Doctor Green at The Harvey Clinic.
好的，在哈维诊所有格林医生。
We always recommend her for babies, because she's very good with them and she runs a special clinic.
我们总为婴儿推荐她，因为她和他们相处的很好，而且她经营一家特殊的诊所。
Oh...actually my youngest child is five, so that wouldn't be any good for us. Right.
事实上，我最小的孩子5岁了，所以这对我们没有帮助。好的。
Is there anywhere else I could try?
还有别的地方我可以试试吗？
Yes, the Eshcol Health Practice is the next one on my list.
是的，我的单子上的下一个是Eshcol健康诊所。
How do you spell that?
怎么拼写？
E-S-H-C-O-L.And it's Doctor Fuller, who has space on his list.
E-S-H-C-O-L。富勒医生，他还有名额。
The clinic only opened a year ago, so the facilities are all very modern. That sounds good.
诊所是一年前刚开的，所以设施很现代。听起来不错。
And it's particularly good if you're busy furing the day, because they also do appointments in the evening.
如果你白天很忙也没有关系，因为他们在晚上也可以预约。
They're closed on Saturday, though.
但是，他们在周六关门。
The only other place on the list is the Health Centre on Shore Lane.
单子上还剩下一个地方是在Shore Lane的健康中心。
You can register with Doctor Gormley, that's G-O-R-M-L-E-Y.
你可以挂戈姆利医生的号，G-O-R-M-L-E-Y。
He's new there, but the centre has a very good reputation.
他是新来的，但是中心的名声很好。
Oh yes, I think I know the road.
是的，我想我知道路线。
That would be the best one. Thanks.
这应该是最好的，谢谢。
Could you tell me, will all their services be free?
你能告诉我，他们的服务都是免费的吗？
Erm...there are usually some small charges that doctors make.
通常医生会有一些小额收费。
Let me see what it says bout the Shore Lane Centre.
让我看看Shore Lane中心是怎么说的。
If you need to be vaccinated before and trips abroad, you won't have to pay for this.Erm, what else?
如果你在去国外旅行之前需要接种疫苗的话，你不需要为此付钱。还有什么呢？
The sports injury treatment service operates on a paying basis, as does the nutritional therapy service.
运动损伤医疗服务需要付费，营养治疗服务也是一样。
Some health centres do offer alternative therapies like homeopathy as part of their pay-to-use service.
一些健康中心提供替代疗法，例如将顺势疗法作为付钱服务的一部分。
Shore Lane are hoping to do this soon - I think they may start with acupuncture.
Shore Lane很快也希望这么做。我认为他们会从针灸开始。
And finally, if you need to prove you're healthy or haven't had any serious injuries before a new employer will accept you,
最后，如果你需要在新雇主录用你之前证明你的健康状况或无严重疾病史，
you can get a free fitness check-up there, but you'd most likely have to pay for insurance medicals though. Okay, thanks.
你可以在那里接受免费的健康检查，但是你可能要付医疗险。